planningfamily.com 2019-05-18

# Privacy Policy

**EverydayFamily, Inc. Privacy Policy**

Privacy Policy Notice

This notice describes EverydayFamily, Inc.’s (EverydayFamily.com) privacy policy (“Notice”). In this privacy policy, we (EverydayFamily Inc., based in Wesley Chapel, FL) describe in detail how we use the information that is collected when visiting www.EverydayFamily.com (the “Site”). By visiting the Site you are accepting the practices described in this Notice.

Please Note: Our Privacy Policy changes from time to time and changes are effective upon posting. Please check back frequently for updates as it is your sole responsibility to be aware of changes. If we make any material changes we will send notification to the e-mail address specified in your account or by means of a notice on this Web Site prior to the change becoming effective.

If you do not agree with the terms of this privacy policy, please do not provide any information to EverydayFamily.com or use any of the services or products offered or provided on [www.EverydayFamily.com](http://www.everydayfamily.com/)

 ** _Types of Information That We Collect_**

Notice: We may gather and use information as follows:

(a) Volunteered Information: We will accept and store any information you enter on the Web Site or give us in any other way that personally identifies you, securely and safely.  We use that information to improve your experience on the Web Site, to get a better general understanding of the type of individuals visiting the Web Site, and to enable us to contact you when needed. Typically you will provide information such as name, email address, postal address, birth date, gender, and due date/baby’s birth date.  This information is used to customize your experience, suggest friends, and provide unique, personalized content just for you.  By submitting this personally identifiable information to EverydayFamily.com, we may disclose Private Information about you with third parties and you agree to receive email and postal mail communication from EverydayFamily and third parties. We are able to offer all of the great content, sweepstakes, samples and coupons on the site by your willingness to accept this communication. This privacy policy applies to users who register on www.EverydayFamily.com or on the websites of our media partners. We believe in 100% permission based marketing. Members always have the option to unsubscribe from these emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link contained in every email sent. Members also have the option of completely removing their information from our database by sending the request to [memberservices@EverydayFamily.com](mailto:memberservices@EverydayFamily.com).

You can always choose not to provide certain information to us, however, you will not be able to take advantage of many of our offers and exciting site features. If you have previously provided certain information to us and you desire to remove such information from our databases, or if you do not wish for your information to be disclosed to third parties, you may contact us at [memberservices@EverydayFamily.com](mailto:memberservices@EverydayFamily.com) to remove such information. If you have requested that this information be sent to third parties for the fulfillment of offers or any other reason, you will have to contact the third party directly to remove or modify your information. We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as our email service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information  _only as necessary_  to provide these services to us.

(b) Automatic Information / Login: To enable us to provide content that users need and desire, we collect aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. A Cookie is simply a small data file we place on your computer's hard drive when you first visit the Web Site (“Cookie”). This file contains an encrypted unique number that helps us identify you when you return to the Web Site. Cookies are employed by thousands of web sites to enhance users' web viewing experience. Cookies can neither damage user files nor can they read information from users' hard drives. Allowing us to create a Cookie on your hard drive will not give us or any other site access to the rest of your computer's hard drive, and only we will be able to read the Cookie that the Web Site creates. Certain features of EverydayFamily.com may not work without use of automatic information collection technologies. Information collected by these technologies cannot be used to identify you without additional identifiable information.

We may also use cookies, pixels, web beacons (which are usually small, transparent graphic images), operating system and device information and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit, the features and information for which you searched and viewed, the email you opened, or on which advertisements you clicked. This type of information is collected to make the Site more useful to you and to tailor the experience with us to meet your special interests and needs.

The use of cookies by our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers is not covered by our privacy policy. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our partners, affiliates, tracking utility company, service providers use session ID cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.

We employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

An “Internet protocol address” or “IP Address” is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer when you use the Internet. We, or our service providers, may use your IP Address when you access the Site or use other means to assist with delivering geographically targeted advertisements.

Most web browsers automatically accept Cookies, but if you prefer, you can edit your browser options to block Cookies in the future. The “Help” portion of the toolbar on most browsers will explain how you can prevent your browser from accepting new Cookies, how to set the browser to inform you when you receive a new Cookie, or how to reject Cookies altogether.

(c) Third-Party Information: We may also combine online and/or offline information received from third parties with the information we have already collected from you via our Site. The third party information is used for a variety of purposes including to verify other information about you (e.g., verify your mailing address to send you requested products or services) and to enhance the content and advertising we provide to you.

(d) Social Networking: You can modify your privacy settings within your My Account screen on the site. By selecting the “Community Preferences” link you can select who can see your profile information and your public messages. If you would like to have an unauthorized profile removed, you can contact us at [memberservices@everydayfamily.com](mailto:memberservices@everydayfamily.com) and we will delete the profile from our records.

(e) Behavioral Advertising: We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site and to collect information from emails for advertising purposes. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp> or <http://www.aboutads.info/choices>.

(f) Display Advertising: We utilize Google Analytics for Display Advertising, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, and Demographics and Interests reporting, including Remarketing to advertise online.  This allows third-party vendors, including Google, to show our ads on sites across the internet.  We use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together, to inform, optimize, and serve ads based on someones's past visits to our website.  These cookies also report ad impressions, interactions with ad services and basic demographic information, such as age, gender and interests.  You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads).

 ** _How this Information is used_**

We use information for personal identification for identify recognition and verification; to provide advertisements from EverydayFamily or our third party marketing partners, such as: product-related and non product-related businesses as well as others that we deem valuable to our members; to get a better general understanding of the type of individuals visiting the Web Site; to respond to your requests for purchases, comments, or questions; to improve your experience at the Web Site; to collect aggregated site-visitation statistics; to alert you to product enhancements, special offers and updated information. We transfer your information to third-parties as needed, at your request, for the purposes of completing offers that you select and for targeted marketing. Your username, avatar, City, State and due date may be used on the Site or in member emails for the purposes of announcing sweepstakes winners or other public announcements and other social networking purposes like helping to identify other members that you may want to connect with.

You can limit the social networking features, the way that we tailor advertising based on your self-reported interests, and other information in your profile by clicking on the “My Account” section of the Site and deleting or modifying the information. Please see the section below on Access and Correction for more information. In addition, you can delete the cookies that we have placed on your browser.

Some or all of the information collected during a promotions, contest, polls, or sweepstakes (“Promotions”) may be disclosed publicly. It may also be shared with other third parties as disclosed at the time of collection or in the Promotion rules. These third parties may include providers of prizes in order to update you of your status of your prize or other fulfillment needs or a co-sponsor who may use your Personal Information to administer the Promotion or for their marketing purposes, but only in conformance with their privacy policy as made available to you at the time of collection. EverydayFamily is not responsible for their privacy policy or practices.

When you participate in a Promotion, you are subject to any official rules for that Promotion, which may contain additional information about the specific privacy practices associated with the Promotion.

 ** _Disclosure of Collected Data_**

  * When you request us to share your personal information with another company, such as signing up for special offers or promotions.
  * We will disclose aggregate level information about our database to marketers as necessary to convey the services that we have the ability to offer, or to report on the advertising campaigns that we have launched over the course of our existence.
  * We may release any user information if required to comply with law; to enforce or to apply the Web Site Terms and Conditions; or under the good faith belief that disclosure is otherwise necessary or advisable including, without limitation, to protect the rights, properties, or safety of us or our users.
  * Our employees and independent contractors have access to some of your personally identifiable information for the purpose of helping us run our business (not for their own purposes). They access and use such data subject to our instructions, on a “need to know” basis and under confidentiality and security agreements.
  * If the Site or business is ever sold, we may disclose your personally identifiable information to a (prospective) buyer on the condition that such buyer agrees to comply with this Privacy Policy.
  * We may share personally identifiable information with third-party companies.
  * We freely use and disclose data in anonymous form, for example, in statistics or reports to our advertising customers.

Please remember that if you post any information in areas of our Site that are generally accessible to users, such as forums, article comments, and photo contests, it will be available to the public.

 ** _Access and Correction_**

We provide you with the ability to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may contact us at [memberservices@everydayfamily.com](mailto:memberservices@everydayfamily.com) with any changes you would like to make to your personal information or if you would like to delete your personal information. For security purposes, we require user verification via user's email address, first and last name, and zip code to update personal information. We will retain your information for as long as your account is active, as needed to provide you services, to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.

 ** _Testimonials_**

With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you want your testimonial removed please contact us.

 ** _Security_**

We protect the security of your personal information. We take steps to protect your data from loss, misuse, alteration, destruction, or unauthorized access. While we use security technologies to secure users' information, we cannot guarantee that any electronic communications is totally secure.

 ** _Information Retention_**

We retain your personal information in our database for as long as you remain a member of EverydayFamily.  As soon as you unsubscribe, your information is removed permanently from our database.  This may not remove your information from third parties if it was previously disclosed to them.

 **Forums and Public Comments**

We may make message boards, comment walls, and other interactive forums available as part of the Site. You should be aware that any information which you post to these interactive forums or otherwise choose to make publicly available, including your Personal Information, may be disclosed and available to all users who have access to that portion of the Site. By using these interactive forums, you agree that we are not responsible for any information that you disclose or communicate in such forums, and any disclosures you make are at your own risk.

 ** _Children_**

Users of the Web Site must be at least 13 years old. If a child has provided us with personal information, that child's parent or guardian should contact us at [memberservices@everydayfamily.com](mailto:info@everydayfamily.com) to delete such information from our records.

 ** _Third Party Web Sites_**

Please be aware that the Web Site may have links to third party web sites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. When you click on one of these third party links, you are entering another web site for which we have no responsibility. You may be directed to a third party website in the process of completing offers on our website and should be aware of this. Always check the privacy policies for each page as you may be on a third party website not owned or operated by EverydayFamily, Inc. This Notice does not cover the information practices or policies of such third party web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all such web sites since their privacy policies may be materially different from our Notice.

 ** _Widgets_**

Our Web Site includes social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the ShareThis button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social media features and widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Web Site. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

 ** _OpenID Provider_**

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.  Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

 ** _Public Forums_**

Our Web Site offers publicly accessible blogs, message boards, comment walls and other community forums as a part of the Site. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas or otherwise choose to make publicly available, including your Personal Information, may be disclosed and available to all users who have access to that portion of the Site. By using these forums, you agree that we are not responsible for any information that you disclose or communicate in such forums, and any disclosures you make are at your own risk. To request removal of your personal information from any of our community forums, please contact us at. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

 ** _Information Retention_**

We retain your personal information in our database for as long as you remain a member of EverydayFamily.  As soon as you unsubscribe, your information is removed permanently from our database.  This may not remove your information from third parties if it was previously disclosed to them.

 ** _Your Agreement and Changes to this Notice_**

By using this site, including, without limitation, submitting information on the registration page, signing up for additional advertiser offers and/or continuing to receive communication from us, you indicate that you have read and understand this Notice and you consent to the collection and use of information by us in the manner explained in this Notice. This Privacy Policy Notice, including without limitation, provisions covering limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and the application of Florida law govern any dispute over privacy. By using and accessing the Web Site you agree to indemnify us for any and all third party claims resulting from your breach of this Notice. If you have any questions or concerns about your privacy at the Web Site, please email a thorough description of the issue to [memberservices@EverydayFamily.com](mailto:memberservices@EverydayFamily.com). If you do not accept this Notice, do not access and use the Web Site. We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, and/or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on the Site. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site or acceptance of our communication following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes and agree to continue receiving communication from us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please unsubscribe by clicking [here](http://www.everydayfamily.com/Unsubscribe.aspx).

 ** _Comments and Questions_** ** __**

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact us at EverydayFamily, Attention: Chief Privacy Officer, 2406 Cypress Glen Dr #101, Wesley Chapel, FL 33544. ** __**

Or call : 1-888-660-6631

 ** _Your California Privacy Rights: A Notice to California Users (California Civil Code Section 1798.83)_**

California’s “Shine the Light” law, Civil Code section 1798.83, requires certain businesses to respond to requests from California customers asking about the business' practices related to disclosing personal information to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes. Alternately, such businesses may have in place a policy not to disclose personal information of customers to third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes if the customer has exercised an option to opt-out of such information-sharing. We have such a policy in place.

Opting out of Direct Mail Marketing: If you do not want us to send you any offers from third parties through direct mail or share your Personal Information with other companies so that they can send you direct mail offers about their products and services, please write to us at the street address set forth in this document or [click here](http://www.everydayfamily.com/contact/). If you write to us, please include your email address, name and mailing address in the body of your letter, and please include “Direct Mail Opt-Out” in the subject line.

Opting out of Email Marketing: If you do not want us to send you emails regarding special promotions or offers or share your Personal Information with other companies so that they can send you emails about their products and services, simply follow the unsubscribe instructions that are located at the bottom of those emails or you can [click here](http://www.everydayfamily.com/unsubscribe/) to manage your newsletter and email marketing preferences.

California customers may request further information about our approach to this law by writing to us at the address provided in the “Comments and Questions” section located in this document.

Opt-Out, Communication Preferences

You may modify your communication preferences and/or opt-out from specific communications at any time. Please specify and adjust your preferences [here](http://www.everydayfamily.com/unsubscribe/). _  
**  
Terms of Use**_

Note also that your use of the Site is subject to our [Terms of Use](http://www.everydayfamily.com/terms/), which contain disclaimers and limitations of liability.  
Updated 08/08/2012
